# A G U S T I N C O R D O B A

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR



## CONTACT

- (351) 7895201
- AGUSTIN.CORDOBA.WORK@GMAIL.COM
- O CORDOBA, NUEVA CORDOBA.
- 🤨 NACIONALITY: ARGENTINA.
- O HTTPS://AGUSWORK.GITHUB.IO/POR TAFOLIO/

#### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / SCSS / Tailwind
- JavaScript
- REACT / Next Js
- FIGMA / Notion
- PHP/Laravel
- SQL
- Git GitHub
- Docker
- NodeJs
- SCRUM / CRUD
- Docker/MongoDB

## AVAILABILITY: FULLTIME

#### IANGHAGF

IELTS (2024)

UNIVERSIDAD BLAS PASCAL

FIRST CERTIFICATE B2 (2017)

INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL OF ENGLISH LA FALDA, CORDOBA RESULT: PASS WITH MERIT

### PROFILE

Front End Developer with experience in personal and professional work, I have two years of professional experience in freelance work from landing pages to MFE's, currently specializing in React, NextJs, Node, MongoDB and Docker. I also work as Fullstack since my professional work demanded it and I could quickly develop and resolve those issues. I also have experience with PHP, MySql, Laravel and some knowledge in Java and Python. I know work methodologies since I count in certain projects like the MFE with the integration of a group which is individualized each one in its own area.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **BWEBLY (2023 - 24)**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER .
WORKING METHOD: SCRUM.
PROGRAMS: REACT, NEXTJS, SCSS.
MORE INFORMATION IN MY PORTFOLIO

#### **DEVLOOSE (2022 - 2023)**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER .
WORKING METHOD: SCRUM.
PROGRAMS: REACT, NEXTJS, SCSS.
MORE INFORMATION IN MY PORTFOLIO

#### LILLEGROUP (2022- 2024)

ENGLISH - CALL CENTER .
WORKED FOR A CARDIOLOGY CENTER FROM EEUU.

#### SYNTESIS (2021)

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER .
WORKING METHOD: SCRUM.
PROGRAMS: PHP, LARAVEL, TAILWIND.

## EDUCATION

**REACT - NEXTJS DEVELOPER (2021 - 22)** 

UDEMY ACADEMY FINAL WORK SCORE: 9

JAVA SCRIPT DEVELOPER (2021)

CODERHOUSE ACADEMY FINAL WORK SCORE: 10

**BACHELOR OF PSYCHOLOGY (2019 - TODAY)** 

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CÓRDOBA.

COURSE: 4TH YEAR